They'll ask you one day to tell them the story of how the world was saved. They'll
want to know how we found our heroes, and together, fought back. But to tell that story, you
young to remember how green the world was, how light, how full of hope. And how we were too
blinded by the light of our own happiness to see the darkness buried right under our own feet.
And when it finally came, it had only one purpose to destroy all that was good.
It was men who fought first, because that's what men do. We fought. We bled. We lost.
So our mothers, our wives, our daughters, our sisters, they picked up the sword. They put on the
sword. And we beat you.
This world has been broken many times. And the breakers are always different.
Sometimes they come from space, sometimes from underground, sometimes they're human. Sometimes
animal. Other times, no form at all, a germ, a disease, and energy. But they bring death,
always death. A death is always followed by rebirth, destruction by renewal. And that first
job in 15 years ago, this age old cycle started again. You see, the stitch was always there.
Mother Earth had just buried it deep, deep down, to protect us, to protect our most cherished creations.
And then we cut down the forest, melted the ice, opened up the stitch, and all the breakers out.
A young lady, just who was telling the story here? Okay, we've told the story a million times,
start. I want to code the x-dory. Well, you had one this morning. So, as I was saying,
the destruction of the boreal forest. Codeiac. How we can do maths? Codeiac. How about algebra?
How could some algebra? How about physics? Codeiac! Okay, silence, silence.
Shh. Willow wins again. This is the story of how Codeiac took out 100 breakers with one swipe
of his mighty axe. It was just the year after the stitch had opened, and our brave forces were
gathered in Glasgow for their first assault. The nights were long and wet and windy. The only thing
that kept them going were these stories. My dad is a born storyteller. He says our stories are
as important as our guns, our swords, especially now. Stories give those of us that are still left,
hope. They inspire our warriors like my mum to keep fighting.
He tells me these things not to scare me, but to remind me that one day they'll need me to tell
the story. The story of how we pulled ourselves away from all this darkness and death and destruction.
And found the lights. They were ready to fight. Were there flowers in the island?
Yeah, there are flowers. Thousands of reds and purples, yellows, colors like you and believe.
The island is so bright. It was so beautiful. Like heaven, heaven. Don't worry,
sounds closer than it really is. Whether animals on the island? Back then, so many.
It'd be, maybe they're still there. Bunnies, bunnies, birds and badgers.
All right, pretty girl. I'm gonna go grab some presents.
You mum? Yeah, baby. We have to go wake up.
Make a wish.
Thank you.
Mom, it's beautiful. That is warm. I'm a little bit cold there, I shouldn't eat it.
There? Where are we going? Okay, my turn. All right, now I know you're not my way
But I am 15. Yeah, it's been seen that you've never had a real one. I thought maybe.
No, you're so cute. I love him. What is it? That's a dog.
You might have been Travis from the nine block makes them. Proceeds go to veterans.
Maybe someday we'll find you a real one. What is name? Well, he's yours now, you name him.
It's time now. We'll make five minutes. Yes sir. Well, fill it up. It sounds awesome. Just close,
boots, thumbs, okay? Yeah, him too. How long will he be gone? Just fill it up, will I?
But does. Is that true, Sally? Is that true, Sally? Is that true, Sally?
Yeah, wow, baby. No, it's okay. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Close that stitch, I don't understand. When close is another one, I don't think so. We can't hold the line anymore.
We lost the earth, but tell you, and do hours to come here, come here, come here.
Close. You know, we've got 15 veterans in this block alone. We can still fight.
You too, you did fight. I can fight again. Listen to me. You get one bite, even a single scrum.
You don't look who's talking. It's been 72 hours, so I'm clear. Yeah, I totally am here, and you know.
I want to help that as you may be. It was an icing on the back.
You. You know, I just did. Well, that's it, that.
It's okay. It's going to be okay.
Hey, hey, quickslaw. Are there any hybrids? Who's this hybrids? If you don't get your last last, you're going to become one. Go on! Go on!
Go on! This one's calling to Mercy Bay, right? Yes, ma'am. Get in.
I need to write in the front. Leave the convoy. What's you going to get there, okay?
Well, what? My mum, where are we going? Dad, where are we?
Somebody save. Come on.
Listen up. And it can hurt your wife. He's too much a sneeze. He's too much a cough.
I've seen it happen if it happens to me. I won't pull the trigger myself.
You know, I do his concern and not us.
You don't have time for that shit?
You know, you're not totally immune. You might have a bad job, so you think you are?
She's right. No one is. We can turn. Sure. Anybody can.
The male brain is simple. Synapse is in straight lines. One language.
The infection burns them out quick. Our synapses are like waves that stretch clear across our
brains. And cross each other multiple times. We're more complicated.
My bread more complicated. Lady, you are a female teenager. You're a damn near and
destructible.
Ready to fight. Just like Koleak.
What about Koleak? He's not a woman. He's killed over 100 breakers. I'm sure he's got scratched. Koleak can
return. He's part breaker himself. 100 breakers. I heard it was 300. What is it matter
the number? Point is he did it? His pet bear killed at least 50. Pet bear. Koleak is a bear.
Look at the bloody hair old. You're wrong. The bear is how he got the name. He raised it from
the cup. He found an anchorage. I died of foot with him. Oh, not it.
By the pattern for every man who said they fought with Koleak. No, it's not a matter.
Isn't a Scottish blitz? I heard nobody got out of that one and escaped. No one did.
Koleak has a bear. You never told me that. Doesn't matter. The story is the zone.
There are no bears to fight like one. Like we need to fight to the claw.
The second little Koleak bear is a fight to Koleak.
I come to the family bear. We'll be there soon, my love. Try and get some sleep.
Stay in the trap!
Go, go!
Come on, you got you. You okay now?
That was the last of them. Come on. What happened? They were honest.
Before we could react, three of them. Get everyone off the road into the forest. It's safer.
Let's go to get out of the road into the forest. Quickly!
Yeah, everyone off the road!
What? Oh, I got five ten minutes. Everyone's different. I'll stay with you till it's over.
Oh, thank you. Your face!
It's okay. It's human, not break. It's not too far. It must be bears.
It's worth to talk a moment. There's maybe five. We'll get there by dawn.
Can you earn? Why? When I raise?
Take my guy. No, he's no point. That'll slow him down at best.
Listen to me. Can you make it through this?
You can't stop. You can be afraid. But you can't let it stop you.
Like what scares you move you forward. You understand?
I love you, Willon.
I have to stand.
Oh, I have to stand. I have to fight.
You said we were going, you said we had to come. They need me.
You said we? You said we?
I need me. I need you.
I need you.
Hold them back. You go!
What's with me?
I'm not that way. He's way. What? What? What? What's out of me to go with them? Move!
They would you call it?
Keep moving. They're almost there.
Have the stories I told you. Back in the day before you were born,
my mom and I would go fishing.
You mean when they were fish? That's what you made those up.
Get that.
That's small, but it's sea worthy.
It's not that small. We could still take a couple of those people with us.
This is our path, not theirs.
But we could help.
Well, this is our path. You and me. We cannot think about anyone else right now, okay?
Come on.
Isn't that how the world breaks?
Please, under the wall.
Hey!
Yours? No. No, we're just checking it, looking for food.
It's your book.
Okay, okay. It's our boat and you're going to get me out of here.
Those things are coming. Come on. Get it in the water.
Okay, we're still going to go very far without petrol.
You don't think I'd leave it here with a tank full of gas steel?
There's someone to steal? No. Motors dry.
So where's the fucking gas?
It's in the boot of one of the cars around the corner.
Okay, come on. Come on.
Stay here. Stay here. Okay, let's go.
Is it just you? Please, no.
Everyone know what it means. What?
What it means is just to let's get his.
Not our wives, not our mothers, not our daughters.
When they have turned, it's now biology and attacks the white chromosome.
It's either. That's what it means.
The world went to revenge. I think you wrote a blame.
Something you just can't wash off.
Open it. Open it. Just get in my key.
Come on. Come on. Let's go.
What about the man?
He got scared. He ran off. Come on. Help me.
What my come? One, two, three.
What do you say, babe? Do you want to get some breakfast?
Hold on tight, babe.
I promise that.
Sorry, Mrs. Time. How long he take three?
You'll see. It's not so bad having just one.
Nothing in the snares?
I'll come on. You're always happy when those traps are empty.
Need to eat, Willa.
Not just tin beans and scraps from the garden and you need protein.
I'm so deusky, honey.
Black.
I told you that climb is too risky.
It was easy to answer. Don't get cocky young lady. Anything happens to you.
All right, take them aside.
I'll leave them when I'm done.
What's the wood on the fire? The dry stuff of wet stuff is too smoky.
Why do you let me spit the wood sometimes?
Huh?
I mean, I can swing an axe like Code Jack taking off a break his head and like you.
Oh yeah, you think so?
What are you trying me?
All right, show me.
Come on.
Show me how you swing that sword. You will not let you split the rest.
You're not ready, Willa. You need more training.
Oh good. Kindly.
Did you see what happened when you first approached me head on like that?
I painted you past and I came in from behind and gave myself the advantage.
Understand?
Come on. I'll call you another.
Maybe some of this fire wouldn't, okay?
That show tonight only. Turn egg omelette.
French green beans. Get it while you can.
What are you doing?
I like the way that she did it.
Can you help me?
Okay, okay.
Did she teach you?
No. I had to learn. I'm watching how I do it.
Just like you're not in watching me.
The hunt to run, to climb, to fight, to survive.
And when this war is over, you'll get to learn the rest.
What's the rest?
To live.
How shall she know where I look like now?
Oh, well. It's only been a year.
Only. She could pass me on the street and she won't recognize me.
I think you're over estimating.
Do you think she's met Kodiak?
Sure. Of course. Why not?
She was Kodiak, she's safe.
Okay.
How is it?
Looks just like how she did it.
Can we eat?
Okay, just one. And then you eat.
Okay, just one story and then we eat.
This is the story of when Kodiak was way up north.
He was collecting firewood for the long, cold winter ahead.
Now remember, for Kodiak, gathering firewood is not like what we do picking up sticks and
drift with no one. He could take down an entire tree with his axe and entire forest.
Now with every blow of that mighty axe,
I know it would run most with a sky.
You only made that axe himself.
We carved the handle from an English oak that had been hit by lightning.
Forged it from steel, from an old Welsh mining ground.
Time and hard, indestructible.
A day, he was heading back to his camp.
He heard something, something no one had ever heard before.
He was the first to see it, the stitch,
and crawl and out of it.
Break yes.
But he wasn't scared.
No, obviously wasn't scared.
He was ready to fight.
Yes, he finally did.
I need to gather 100 breakers with one swipe of his mighty axe.
Well, it was one breaker, actually.
But it was the first.
Many more came after we know that.
But this was the first and this is how we learned that to kill them.
You have to take off his hands.
Dika, are you ready to do it?
Not the only way.
The fastest bullets work, but they're not as effective.
Slows them down, but it doesn't kill them at the end.
Time for dinner.
These stories.
Yeah?
About cardiac.
You know them so well.
Where every parent does.
Are you sure?
What?
He's not you.
We're not.
Well, it sounds like you. Strong, powerful.
This is an axe.
Oh, please, go on.
Go on.
Where an eye ford.
We would go into battle knowing there was a giant out there
where an axe made of lightning,
slicing through breakers like a hot knife through butter.
Cardiac gives us hope.
If he could stand tall, if he could save this world from breaking.
Maybe you could.
Because he's totally you.
Well,
these stories are important.
We need to keep telling them how the stitch opened,
how the first breakers came then the hybrids and how we stood tall.
How we fought back, found our heroes.
And one day,
when this world is bright and green and alive again,
we will go back.
Believe her?
Oh, yes, I do.
Because when I look at you,
and then mine did.
Well,
hope.
Now, I'll have your dinner.
Pause here.
Oh,
Stix is warmer.
No, she doesn't have furlates.
This is fighting, but where is he?
Not so peaceful.
They can't see us coming.
No, they don't see like we do.
I don't think they have eyes.
I think I've other senses once we don't have.
The hybrids are the breakers used them as their eyes and ears,
kind of like they're connected somehow.
You know, brains are braiding.
But they don't know where, here, right, on this island.
If they did my love, they wouldn't be on this island.
What about the landlines?
Just a precaution.
Just don't be breakers.
Just stop anyone.
You know, it's up. You're going to need your energy.
Why did they want to hear us? If we didn't do anything to them?
Remember our lessons about insects and
I'm going to kill the wasp. We're trying to invade there until.
Yeah.
Oh, maybe it's like that.
They think we're like the wasp.
Trying to invade their home.
So they eliminate the threat.
Us.
It's our home, too.
Not it is. That it is.
We're going to be ready to fight for it.
Are you ready to fight?
I got...
33 seconds.
Can't you hear them? The breakers are coming.
What are you doing here, my horn?
Get to the cottage.
28 seconds.
Which direction is the cottage from the white cliffs?
No.
How far?
We're both miles.
Faster than I could come on.
Don't shoot breakers.
The hybrids are coming.
They're coming for you little dog.
Save me, will I? Save me.
59.
Thanks to directions to the bunkers.
No, no.
They're behind you.
Come on.
Come on. Almost there.
In a tent.
How do you kill a breaker?
Oh, decab. Show me.
And a hybrin?
Decab.
No, not enough.
Brains.
No, not 22.
It's not bad.
But you could do better.
You'll act my good.
What are you about?
Okay.
Oh, no.
On your mark.
Get set.
Come on, nugget!
You're a ward.
Dying?
For not quitting.
Oh, bug is it?
Oh, I wish it were.
More protein.
What are they?
Strawberries.
Trivan.
I think I've always grown wild here.
It's just assumed they died out with everything else.
It's silent, it's special.
Somehow, they're still holding on.
Spit them.
No.
You have them all.
I've tried them before.
No, not there.
Just the red bit.
Yeah.
Uh.
I still have precious.
It's to be a lot more of them back in the old days.
Strawberries?
Places.
Your mum.
When we got married, just before you were born before the stitch.
All she wanted for the wedding party was strawberry, shortcake.
What is stupid, okay?
It's a yellow cake, sweet whipped cream, and dozens of the house.
dozens?
Did she like them?
Like them?
She ate the whole damn cake.
Didn't even come for anyone else.
She was the...
She is the life of the party.
Always has been.
That she loves strawberries.
Like you do, apparently.
I can't believe it doesn't think I'm ready yet.
Yeah, just don't worry about her.
To fight.
To fight like mum fights.
You don't know.
He just thinks that I can't do or he did to that man.
But I could fight.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
He's okay, he just...
Okay, no, you're fine.
You're okay, just don't move.
I take his step back, okay? I just...
He's like my legs.
Okay, you did you want?
Okay.
I'm too...
Okay, okay, don't move.
Let's get back from this.
Okay, um...
Okay, you're okay.
Do you want to tell me what happened?
Are you alone?
Is someone out there?
Is anybody over there?
No, it's fine, okay.
Uh... no, okay, you know what, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna take you someplace more.
Let's... let's go to this one.
Okay, just a little further.
Stay right here.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Let's get you warmed up.
Here you go.
Drink something.
He must be thirsty.
Are you bleeding?
Just hit my head on the boat.
What boat?
We were headed up the coast to my grandma's house.
He said it'd be safe for there.
Something came up from below.
Just over.
A dad, a brother.
We all went in the water.
We didn't know they could swim and I was big.
Okay, okay, now.
I'm willing.
I was your name.
Gross.
Did everyone ask me about it?
It's the last time you ate Rosie.
Okay.
This is what I have left.
I'm going to go and get you some real food, okay?
No.
It's okay, you need to eat.
You need protein.
You have to do as make sure the fight keeps going.
I can't.
We have to do as put a log on and make sure it doesn't die.
Please don't leave.
Okay.
I'll stay.
You're free this longer.
Where are you going?
You're game.
You don't have much time. Let's go.
They're waiting at the bus.
Mom, we need to go now. There's no time.
But what about Dad? We can't just leave.
Dad, we need to get him.
We need soldiers. We're warriors like you.
You can't fight anymore. You can.
Mom, what's wrong? Aren't you ready?
I... I told you.
I'm sorry.
We're not... don't leave me, you know?
No matter how bad you ask, we may be.
You've been gone all day.
I got scoured the island. I blew the horn. Didn't you hear it?
It was... I fast deep in the pangrove.
Because of all the trailing. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Sit down. Make you some food.
You might have noticed it's not easy surviving out here.
The tin fruit has gone. The garden has spent.
We are living on fumes, well.
We have to be careful. We have to be smart.
That gun. It was that man's, wasn't it?
We left a wrong behind that night we came here.
Did never choice, not that night.
Mom did.
What?
Had a choice?
Could you choose to leave us?
I'm had to leave. To save the world and I had to save you.
Are you all bad?
What?
And then, are you all bad? Because you can turn and we got?
No, I'm not.
Of course not.
Not all men are bad.
And girls can turn, too, remember.
It's just less likely.
Baby, kill breakers.
Of course. I told you the stories.
When it comes to it, if it comes to it, you will too.
Hi, Brits.
Yes, but it's not so easy. They will want us.
Would you kill a person?
If they threatened you or mom, in any way?
Yes, I would.
Right.
You need to eat some soup.
Okay, slow down. I don't have many of those. It's better to save me.
Do you live here?
Oh, no. I just let me have some time to get away.
It's like a girl cave.
Are you alone? Like me?
Yeah.
Where do you live? Really?
Come.
You want to see something?
Sure.
This is what the world used to look like for the stitch opened.
Okay, one looks so happy.
Yeah.
It is.
I dad said he's a good fish.
Fish?
What are these?
I don't know.
He's sort of like breakers.
The ones that they were flowers back then.
Thousands of colors you've never seen.
Everything is alive.
The world is bright and beautiful.
I miss my dad and my brother.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hopefully out there right now, looking for you.
What's his name?
Bear.
He's a dog.
He's a dog, but I call him Bear because he fights a codiac.
A codiac is dead.
What?
Well, if he were alive, he could do all the things they say.
We don't want by now.
He can't do it on his own.
He needs a help too.
Do you like stories?
This is the story about codiac and the first battle breakers.
It was after the first stage opened and already codiac was a leader among men.
codiac and the men slayed every single breaker that came at them.
We thought we were on the battle.
This is when they realized that breakers weren't only enemy.
We were also fighting with ourselves.
So, codiac killed the first hybrid.
Yep. And he told us how to do it.
I've got to mush the brains.
I think I'll stop them.
That's right.
It's a good year, it's not dead.
He's out there fighting for us and with us.
And together we're going to close that stitch.
And the world won't be broken anymore.
You'll see.
And then I go, I'll be back soon with some more food.
Will you be okay?
This is for you.
I'll keep you warm.
When can I leave?
Soon.
Come on!
30-3 seconds, faster!
That's one yet!
Come on, now get hit it!
Stay on that log.
Focus! Keep going!
Come on!
That's my girl!
Keep a bit of this! Come on, Willah!
It's under a minute!
Keep going!
It's your best time yet.
What are you thinking about?
The break is a hybrid.
Just kill them!
Good.
You just take up four breakers.
Now...
There's a hybrid coming.
I take you. They take you. They take you.
It's not mud.
Come on!
Come on, then.
Daddy, you okay?
I'm not your daddy!
Do you need help?
Hi, Brit!
Hi, Brit! Don't!
I didn't want to save you, little pig!
Come out! Come out! Wherever you!
Dad!
Are you okay?
Give me my stack or you.
Okay.
You might have some soup, okay?
No.
Dad.
I'm fine.
You're not eating.
Of course I'm eating.
No.
You're not eating, so I can eat.
Well, we have to keep rationing until she comes.
You know what if she doesn't?
Don't say that.
What if they lose the war?
Then you would have kept me here for what?
For nothing.
Not nothing.
I'm just supposed to stay here,
carrying around rocks, swinging about a wooden sword,
training me for a war you won't even let me fight.
I am not just training you to fight, will I?
I'm training you to live.
How is this living?
This is like a prison.
We stay here and do nothing.
What's other mothers?
Five years.
Five years, I fought.
And your mother is still out there fighting.
We lost everything, will I?
Everything.
Don't ever say we did nothing.
I'm sorry.
She loved you very much.
Then why isn't she here?
I promised your mom.
I wouldn't give this to you until you were ready.
Yesterday, you proved that.
This was mine.
And now it's yours.
I will show you how to fight like she does.
I'm going to go check the rabbit slers.
Great.
Rabbit's due for lunch, then.
I'm back.
Happy like Sardine.
Oh, I want to see.
No.
Rosie?
Rosie, why would you do this to bear?
But you're okay.
Let go. Come on.
You look at you.
Did it hurt?
Are you scratched?
What did it hurt?
What did I do?
Listen to me.
None of that matters now.
It called out to them.
It's signal to them.
You remember what I told you?
The breakers and the hybrids, they are connected.
They know we are here now, so we leave.
What were we going?
But go.
Hey.
This is what you're trying for, Willa.
The breakers are coming and they will destroy everything here
and it looks like they are.
We're going back.
We're going home.
No.
We've got someone.
And it's just not here.
Dad, I'm scared.
You and that, what scares you?
Of you, for what?
Remember?
We're on the wrong side of the island.
Along the hike up and over to the other side.
You never told me they could swim.
The predator's well.
When they say it's praying, nothing's going to stop.
And we're going to go.
I'd like to come ashore on the beach because it's less rocky.
The mind should sort them down a bit.
You have a time to get to the coast.
We're still moving.
You have those explosions and means we don't have a lot of time.
10, 15 minutes of most.
But we get to the boat.
What are we going to go?
South.
Keep the main land to the left.
And we keep going.
South is our safest land.
No.
My leg.
Let's just rest here.
Just for a bit.
Why are you doing fine?
Once we're through the prime forest,
another five minutes down into the coast.
Where's your head?
I gave it to her.
Now I was just trying to help.
God.
God is on my phone.
Now.
This world.
What's happened?
None of it is your fault.
You understand?
Yeah.
And what happened to that girl?
It wasn't her fault either.
It just happened.
Yeah.
Eat this.
I'll keep you warm.
Five minutes and we go.
Do you want a story?
No.
Who are you?
What if you don't with my daughter?
Not like the others.
Not a courteous story.
I went from the floor.
The floor?
The story without?
That was how to tell.
So why you need to tell them?
Already they were wrong.
They were going to be wrong.
These are the awful things happening up north.
Entire towns ravaged.
People slaughtered by an enemy we did not yet understand.
But we didn't care about any of it.
We were happy.
I never met anyone with so much light.
So much love.
We knew that no matter what should come, we had each other, and we couldn't wait to bring
you into this world. And when you finally came, this little lamb, suffering of trust and
under, he didn't pray, he didn't scream, he hadn't no fear, just for that small amount of moments.
Don't break up. You told me it was going to be hard. What a nice of you told me hard.
I know that you're out there. I know that you're coming back.
Please, if you can make it to the run.
Back to me.
Help me.
Save her.
There. We go back.
It's no fun. It's keep this way.
We'll be there soon.
Here we go. Go, go. Through there.
You did this?
What?
You didn't go to the only one who can chop down a tree with a single blow.
The breakers aren't big enough to get across this. They'll have to go around, which should buy us a few minutes.
Unless we can't get over it.
Come on, maggot. You first work the plank.
You've done this a million times. Come on.
Eyes on the tree.
Are you ready? Focus on the front?
Focus?
Okay.
Please, okay?
No, stay there.
That's the brains. Remember?
That was a brother.
Any bites? Scratches? Any blood?
Good. Go. Go.
Can you make it? Can you get over it?
Hey. Who trained him?
Come on, get up.
Get up.
I'm going to get up now.
I can't.
You could do this.
This is what you're trained for.
I can't help you.
She's still there.
I cannot help you, darling.
You remember how to prime and start the motor like I showed you?
I guess?
You guess? You do what you don't.
Yes, I do.
You cut the moring rope.
It's just one swipe, it's just slide down on it.
It's only one even need to push it.
Dad, you come on.
No.
You said to me.
I don't give you as much time as I can, so you can get to the boat and go.
I will hold them off.
No, I can't stand. I'm going to fight.
I know you could fight.
You've already proved that to me, not today.
Not now.
Let me do this for you.
You are a warrior will.
So you fight.
But don't forget to love.
You can love it all.
Leave it to darkness.
This world is so broken.
I can't do it.
The world is a broken world.
It has ruined it.
Go.
Please, go.
Will it go?
One swipe of the shot!
No.
No!
I'm sorry.
They asked you one day to tell them the story.
Of how the world was saved.
And you tell them.
It was a girl named Willer, who was strong, full of hope and fear.
Willer was scared of what was to come.
But she was ready.
Because like in all good stories,
Willer had a hero.
And when they want to know if Kodiak is just a story, you'll tell them.
Kodiak is real.
The hero who gave Willer hope.
The hero who gives all of us hope.
Come on, man.
This will be the story of how the world didn't break.